

CONTACT

Mobile: +380 50 4411801 E-mail: Zorger27@GMail.com Skype: anatoliy.zorin

Linkedin:

linkedin.com/in/anatolii-zorin

Github:

github.com/Zorger27

PORTFOLIO:Zorin.Expert

ANATOLII ZORIN

Frontend Developer (Vue.js) —

My acquaintance with the world of IT began **in 1992** with the languages *Basic*, *Pascal* and *Fortran*.

At university and after, I studied and worked with *FoxPro* and *1C* languages. Thanks to working with vending machines, I had to learn the *Assembly* language.

Since 2016, I have combined the administrative work as CEO with the work of Digital Marketer (Google Ads, Analytics, SEM), Web Designer (Photoshop, Illustrator, Figma) and Frontend Developer (Javascript/HTML/CSS).

In 2020, I took up intensive study of Backend (*Java*, *Scala*, *Kotlin*).

In 2021, I restored and updated my knowledge of Frontend (Vue, Angular, React).

In 2022, I continued my IT education (*PHP*, *Python*, *Ruby*). **In 2023**, I studied special IT technologies (Three.js, Gatsby, GraphQL).

I'm easy learning. I have good analytical skills. I'm comfortable working in a team or solo.

PROJECTS

- My Curriculum VITAE (Landing page)

Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, Grid CSS, JavaScript

- My Portfolio (SPA)

Technologies: Three.js, Vue.js, VueX, Axios, TypeScript

Rotating 3D cube №2 (SPA)

Technologies: Three.js, Orbit controls, Vue.js, TypeScript

HARD SKILLS

✓ Html5, CSS3, JavaScript, Vue.js, Angular, Three.js
 ✓ Git, Github, Figma, Photoshop

SOFT SKILLS

√ Management, Negotiation

✓ Strategic Thinking, Critical Thinking

LANGUAGES

English - Upper-Intermediate Spanish - Upper-Intermediate

EDUCATION

11.2020 - Until now

ITVDN - IT Video Developers Network

Java Developer, PHP Developer,

Python Developer, Ruby Developer, HTML Coder,

JavaScript Developer, Angular Developer, React Developer, Frontend Developer

11.2021 - Until now

EnglishDom - English language

Pre-Intermediate, Intermediate, Upper-Intermediate

04.2017 - 11.2017

PROG.kiev.ua

Web-Designer (UI/UX Designer), Frontend Developer 09.1994 - 01.1999

Kyiv national university of trade and economics

Accounting and Auditing

EXPERIENCE

13.01.2023 - Until now

Self Employed - Web Developer (Vue.js | Three.js) *Creation and maintenance of sites and applications.*

Tasks: Creation of a site prototype. Website design development. Building a website (SPA) on Vue.js with using TypeScript. Domain name registration.

Connecting a domain name to a site. Connecting Google Analytics 4.0. Registration of the site in Google Search Console and its subsequent indexing. Creation of Sitemap.xml and Robots.txt files. Animation of text, blocks. Creating 3D models using Three.js.

27.12.2016 - 13.01.2023

Yugov & D Ltd - CEO

Full administrative management of the enterprise.

<u>Tasks:</u> Creation of a company logo. Website layout creation. Work with CMS Joomla. Setting up and launching advertising campaigns in Google, YouTube, Facebook, Instagram. Creation of informative video clips for YouTube. Connecting the site with the Google Merchant Center. Registration in Google Map. Programming the coffee roaster.

15.01.2001 - 13.01.2023

LIS Ltd - CEO

Full administrative management of the enterprise.

<u>Tasks:</u> Creation of a company logo. Website layout creation. Work with CMS WordPress. Translation of vending machine messages from German into Ukrainian (translation was done using **Assembler**). Development of accounting for vending machines. Setting up employees' computers. Setting up a local network.

1. JAVA DEVELOPER (TP31617068D | 12.04.2021)

- 1) Java Starter (TP41734788 | 17.06.2021)
- 2) Java Essential (TP85302318 | 16.01.2021)
- 3) Java Advanced 2021 (TP73439317 | 11.08.2021)
- 4) SOLID principles in Java (TP00933660 | 14.12.2020)
- 5) Unit testing with JUnit (TP52431470 | 23.03.2021)
- 6) Java Database Connectivity (TP57486314 | 28.02.2021)
- 7) JDBC & Hibernate (TP00684634 | 04.03.2021)
- 8) Java EE Basic (TP12409765 | 16.03.2021)
- 9) Spring Framework (TP05064920 | 08.02.2021)
- 10) Spring MVC (TP41523672 | 14.02.2021)
- 11) Spring Data (TP19471428 | 27.03.2021)
- 12) Spring Security (TP52120949 | 29.03.2021)
- 13) Web Services Development (TP14941346 | 12.04.2021)
- 14) Jenkins (TP93023078 | 15.06.2021)
- 15) Thymeleaf Patterns Engine (TP16212701 | 17.04.2021)
- 16) Scala Starter (TP28012733 | 02.04.2021)
- 17) Scala Essential (TP41881134 | 07.04.2021)
- 18) Scala Advanced (TP70826526 | 05.05.2021)
- 19) Kotlin (TP51225757 | 25.04.2021)
- 20) Asynchronous programming (TP33405544 | 28.09.2021)
- 21) Design Patterns in Java (TP37097304 | 06.11.2021)

2. PHP DEVELOPER (TP88892276D | 30.09.2022)

- 1) PHP 8.0 Starter (TP45675166 | 17.08.2022)
- 2) PHP 7.4 Essential (TP92998740 | 01.09.2022)
- 3) PHP Advanced (TP47801691 | 28.09.2022)
- 4) Laravel (TP85284868 | 10.09.2022)
- 5) Magento 2 (TP17795504 | 14.09.2022)
- 6) YII2 Essential (TP21584504 | 22.09.2022)
- 7) YII2 Advanced (TP21335122 | 26.09.2022)
- 8) Symfony Web Development (TP16870523 | 30.09.2022)

3. PYTHON DEVELOPER (TP45473683D | 16.11.2022)

- 1) Python 3.8.6 Starter (TP34890769 | 07.10.2022)
- 2) Python 3.8.6 Essential (TP37206931 | 18.10.2022)
- 3) Python Advanced (TP30334066 | 25.10.2022)
- 4) Flask (TP35918152 | 28.10.2022)
- 5) Django Starter (TP36453931 | 10.11.2022)
- 6) Django Essential (TP28729679 | 16.11.2022)

4. Ruby Developer (TP63925579D | 30.11.2022)

- 1) Ruby Essential (TP72010831 | 21.11.2022)
- 2) Ruby Advanced (TP80374246 | 22.11.2022)
- 3) Ruby on Rails (TP69956445 | 29.11.2022)

OTHER CERTIFICATES

- 1) Git basics (TP37589708 | 18.03.2021)
- 2) Docker (TP56750315 | 04.05.2023)
- 3) Linux administration (TP03316433 | 12.10.2021)
- 4) Windows administration (TP18727720 | 31.05.2023)
- 5) Golang (TP09903227 | 22.10.2021)
- 6) Node.js Essential (TP97104275 | 12.03.2024)

1. HTML CODER (TP24303907D | 16.06.2021)

- 1) HTML5&CSS3 Starter 2022 (TP37225065 | 09.08.2022)
- 2) HTML5&CSS3 Essential (TP24244286 | 16.06.2021)
- 3) HTML5&CSS3 Advanced (TP92660322 | 04.06.2021)
- 4) PUG template designer (TP46286417 | 26.10.2023)
- 5) CSS Flexbox (TP01289491 | 09.05.2023)
- 6) Layout of pages using Grid (TP62170279 | 31.05.2021)
- 7) Bootstrap 4 (TP33638993 | 27.05.2021)
- 8) Practical Landing Course (TP73961983 | 09.06.2021)
- 9) WordPress Starter (TP68763365 | 10.07.2021)
- 10) WordPress Essential (TP85465557 | 13.07.2021)

2. JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER (TP84806711D | 01.07.2021)

- 1) JavaScript Starter (TP47415802 | 14.05.2021)
- 2) JavaScript Essential 2021 (TP26716836 | 22.07.2021)
- 3) JavaScript Patterns (TP95784000 | 25.06.2021)
- 4) ECMAScript 6 (TP61852573 | 28.06.2021)
- 5) JavaScript Extended (TP59539891 | 30.06.2021)

3. Angular Developer (TP31003654D | 02.08.2021)

- 1) TypeScript Fundamentals (TP81113114 | 21.03.2021)
- 2) Angular 2.0 Essential (TP75000423 | 29.07.2021)
- 3) Angular 11.0 Essential (TP23149294 | 16.08.2021)
- 4) Angular Advanced (TP01762348 | 02.08.2021)

4. REACT DEVELOPER (TP37723782D | 09.08.2021)

- 1) React Essential 2023 (TP87727177 | 06.09.2023)
- 2) React Advanced (TP74208807 | 09.08.2021)
- 3) React Native (TP06814422 | 19.08.2021)

5. Frontend Developer (TP77692345D | 12.08.2021)

- 1) Vue.js Starter 2023 (TP70934717 | 05.09.2023)
- 2) Vue.js Essential (TP51164572 | 17.08.2021)
- 3) Building site with Vue.js (TP29746655 | 23.08.2021)
- 4) jQuery 2021 (TP55404559 | 23.09.2021)
- 5) Web Components (TP75653206 | 30.07.2021)

6. UX/UI DESIGNER

- 1) UX/UI Design Starter (TP08523730 | 18.05.2021)
- 2) UX/UI Design Essential (TP37142600 | 20.05.2021)
- 3) UX/UI Mobile App Design (TP57418431 | 23.05.2021)
- 4) Figma. Online store design (TP46637985 | 25.07.2021)

7. DATABASE DEVELOPER

- 1) Transact SQL (TP71375264 | 26.01.2021)
- 2) MySQL (TP99655661 | 23.02.2021)
- 3) PostgreSQL (TP84560502 | 20.04.2021)
- 4) MongoDB (TP56496721 | 21.04.2021)
- 5) SQL Essential (TP98353860 | 18.06.2023)

8. PROJECT MANAGEMENT

- 1) Introduction to PM (TP84744235 | 27.04.2021)
- 2) Scrum and PM Methodologies (TP14623786 | 15.02.2021)

9. ENGLISH LANGUAGE

- 1) English for IT (TP23856842 | 05.09.2023)
- 2) Business English (TP45420598 | 04.09.2023)
- 3) Intermediate level of English (Intermediate | 09.01.2022)
- 4) English for advanced (Upper-Intermediate | 14.02.2022)